Guide to the Johan Kugelberg hip hop collection, circa 1975-1985, 2008.
Kugelberg, Johan hip hop collection,
- Series I. Sound Recordings (1-24)
  - LPs - SR 466-520 (Box 10)
    - Parents of Roxanne / Gigolo Tony, Lacey Lace, Anthony Keller Performed by: Gigolo Tony, Lacey Lace, and Anthony Keller, 1985; SR-516 (Box 10)
      Track listing: The parents of Roxanne (vocal) -- The parents of Roxanne (scratch dub instrumental)
    - Guardian angel is watching over us Performed by: Golden Flamingo Orchestra, featuring Margo Williams, ca. 1980; SR-517 (Box 10)
    - Butt of course-- Performed by: Jimmy Castor Bunch, featuring the Everything Man, 1974; SR-518 (Box 10)
      Track listing: E-man boogie -- Bertha butt boogie -- One precious word -- Hallucinations -- Potential -- You make me feel brand new -- Daniel -- Let's party now
    - Official adventures of Grandmaster Flash / Flash Performed by: Grandmaster Flash, 2002; SR-519 (Box 10)
      Track listing: Flash tears the roof off (Grandmaster Flash turntable mix) -- The Mexican (Babe Ruth) -- Flash got more bounce (Grandmaster Flash turntable mix) -- Do what you gotta do (Eddie Drennon & the BBS Orchestra) -- Trans Europe Express (Kraftwerk) -- Computer games (Yellow Magic Orchestra) -- Get off your horse & jam! (Grandmaster Flash turntable mix)
    - White lines (don't, don't do it); Melle Mel's groove Performed by: Grandmaster & Melle Mel, 1983; SR-520 (Box 10)
  - LPs - SR 521-573 (Box 11)
    - Shall we dance (electric slide): Slice, I get nice / Grandmaster Slice & Izzy Chill Performed by: Grandmaster Slice, 1995; SR-521 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Creative Funk
    - Crazy cuts / Grandmixer D St Performed by: Material and Grandmixer D. St.; mixed by Dave Jerden, 1983; SR-522 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Crazy cuts (short version) (3:50) -- Crazy cuts (long dub) (6:50) -- Crazy cuts (long version) (8:08).
    - Crack killed Applejack / [words & music by Mitch McDowell] Performed by: General Kane, 1986; SR-523 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Gordy
      Track listing: Crack killed Applejack (band 1, LP version) -- Crack killed Applejack (band 2, single edit) -- Crack killed Applejack (band 1, club mix) -- Applejack's theme (band 2).
    - White lines (don't don't do it) / Grandmaster and Melle Mel Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and Melle Mel, 1983; SR-524 (Box 11)
      Track listing: White lines (don't don't do it) -- Bonus -- Bonus break -- White lines (don't don't do it) (short version)
    - Home of hip hop Performed by: D. St.; with other musicians, 1985; SR-525 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Celluloid
      Track listing: The home of hip hop -- Hip hop dub -- Hip hop short.
    - Crazy cuts / Grandmixer D St; featuring vocals by Bernard Fowler Performed by: Material and Grandmixer D. St.; mixed by Dave Jerden, 1983; SR-526 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Crazy cuts (long version) -- Crazy cuts (long dub)
    - Grandmixer cuts it up! / Infinity and Grandmixer D St Performed by: Infinity and Grandmixer D. St, 1982; SR-527 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Grandmixer cuts it up! (cut side) -- Grandmixer c.i.u.! (uncut side)
    - Hip hop music Performed by: Groove B Chill, 1990; SR-528 (Box 11)
      Publisher: A&M
      Track listing: Hip hop music (groovy 7" version) -- Hip hop music ("B" dub version) -- Hip hop music (chillin' acappella) -- Hip hop music ("U" can't get enough LP version) -- Hip hop music (booming instrumental).
    - Guci boys / Block Head Performed by: Blockhead, ca. 1985; SR-529 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Roebuck Records
      Track listing: Guci boys (long version) -- Guci boys (dub version) -- Guci boys (instrumental)
    - Truth is on its way / Nikki Giovanni Performed by: Nikki Giovanni, accompanied by the New York Community Choir, 1974; SR-530 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Right-On Records
      Track listing: Poetry from, "Black feeling, Black talk, Black judgment" (Published by William Morrow and Co.) and "Re:creation" (Published by Broadside Press) with "My tower", unpublished. Great Pax Whitey; Peace be still -- Nikki Rosa; It is well -- My tower; Pretty little baby -- Alabama poem; I've decided to make Jesus my choice -- Ego tripping -- All I gotta do; I stood on the banks of Jordan -- Second rapp poem; This little light of mine -- Poem for Aretha; Nobody knows the trouble I've seen -- Woman poem; Amazing grace -- Poem for a lady of leisure now retired; Must Jesus bear the cross alone.
    - Phase two / Jimmy Caster Bunch Performed by: Jimmy Castor Bunch, 1972; SR-531 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Fanfare (Prologue) -- Say Leroy (The creature from the Black Lagoon is your father) -- Luther the anthropoid (Ape man) -- Party life -- When? -- Paradise -- The first time ever I saw your face -- Tribute to Jimi. Purple haze; Foxey lady -- Fanfare (Epilogue).
    - Maximum stimulation / Jimmy Castor Bunch Performed by: Jimmy Castor Bunch, 1977; SR-532 (Box 11)
      Track listing: E-man par-tay -- Maximum stimulation -- Equal people -- Mind power -- TR-7 -- Magnolia -- The return of Leroy (pt. 1) -- The return of Leroy (pt. 2) -- It was you -- Mandy.
    - Supersound Performed by: Jimmy Castor Bunch featuring the Everything Man, 1975; SR-533 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Supersound -- King kong -- Bom bom -- A groove will make you move -- Drifting -- Magic in the music -- What's best?
    - Royal rappin's / Millie Jackson & Isaac Hayes Performed by: Isaac Hayes and Millie Jackson, vocals; with instrumental and vocal acc, 1979; SR-534 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Polydor/Spring
      Track listing: Sweet music, soft lights, and you -- Feels like the first time -- You never cross my mind -- Love changes -- I changed my mind -- Do you wanna make love -- If I had my way -- If you had your way -- You needed me.
    - Sir Coxsone & Duke Reid in concert at Forresters Hall Performed by: Sir Coxsone and Duke Reid, ca. 1975; SR-535 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Studio 1
      Track listing: Milk lane hop -- Duke & the Sir -- Don't do it -- Five minutes on Beeston Street -- Grandma, Grandpa -- Shocker's hop -- I'll find love -- Swanee River rock -- Dukies cooking -- Twilight zone -- Blackberry brandy -- Cool breeze -- What makes honey -- Pink lane hop -- Pink champain -- What a world
    - Prince Jazzbo in the 70tes Volume 1 Performed by: Roots Radics Band, New Extablishment, The Aggrevators, Studio One Band; vocals by Prince Jazzbo, Burning Spear, Larry Marshall, and others, 1999; SR-536 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Carter Music House
      Track listing: School -- Crab walking -- Wise shepherd -- Pepper rock -- Cankie bine -- I Roy you a boy -- Kick bwoy face -- Plum plum -- Mr. Harry -- Gal boy I Roy -- Jah dread -- Every nigger -- Bag a wolfe -- Natty dread long time -- Jamaican kallie -- Wise man
    - Choice of version Performed by: Prince Jazzbo, ca. 1975; SR-537 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Imperial I -- Jah dread -- School -- Fire coal version -- Takeover dub -- Choice of version -- Fool for love -- Rock for dub -- Dub from the skies -- Impossible -- Pepper -- Jah dip -- Apollo 13 -- Night owl
    - Let it out Performed by: Jimmy Castor Bunch, 1978; SR-538 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Drive
      Track listing: Let it out -- Bertha Butt encounters Vadar -- Future place -- The real McCoy -- Sweettooth -- The mystery of me -- My brightest day -- Time -- She's all I need -- You light up my life.
    - It's just begun / The Jimmy Castor Bunch Performed by: Jimmy Castor Bunch, 1972; SR-539 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Creation (Prologue) -- It's just begun -- Troglodyte (Cave man) -- You better be good (or the devil gon' getcha) -- Psyche -- L.T.D. (Life, truth & death) -- My brightest day -- Bad -- I promise to remember -- Creation (Epilogue)
    - Rub-a-dub style / Papa Michigan & General Smiley Performed by: Errol Bennett ("General Smiley") and Anthony Fairclough ("Papa Michigan"), ca. 1975; SR-540 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Rub a dub style -- Nice up the dance -- Thank you Jah -- Compliment to studio one -- Time to be happy -- Eye of danger.
    - Rappin all over / The Marvelous Three & The Younger Generation Performed by: Marvelous Three and the Younger Generation (D. Parker, A. O'Bryant, and J. Cochran), 1980; SR-541 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Rappin all over (rap side) -- Rappin all over (music side)
    - Ya mama / WUF Ticket Performed by: WUF Ticket (J. Mason, M. Ahmed, E. McField, K. Wolf), 1982; SR-542 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Prelude Records
      Track listing: Ya mama (vocal) -- Ya mama (instrumental)
    - Ya mama / WUF Ticket Performed by: WUF Ticket (J. Mason, M. Ahmed, E. McField, K. Wolf), 1982; SR-543 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Jupiter Records
    - You and me together Performed by: Vicki Anderson, 1981; SR-544 (Box 11)
      Track listing: You and me together (long version) -- You and me together (rapp) -- You and me together
    - Rapture rappin / [Blondie] Performed by: Blondie, ca. 1985; SR-545 (Box 11)
      Publisher:
    - Party on the corner / Vaughan Mason and Butch Dayo Performed by: Vaughan Mason, 1983; SR-546 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Party on the corner -- Party on the corner (master dub version).
    - Full story of Roxanne / UTFO Performed by: UTFO, 1985; SR-547 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Metronome
      Track listing: Roxanne, Roxanne (U.T.F.O.) -- Hanging out (voc.) (U.T.F.O.) -- Roxanne, Roxanne (inst.) (U.T.F.O.) -- The real Roxanne (Roxanne with U.T.F.O.) -- Roxanne's back side (scratch it) (Roxanne with U.T.F.O.) -- The real Roxanne (Roxanne with U.T.F.O.).
    - Bite it / UTFO Performed by: UTFO, 1985; SR-548 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Select Records
      Track listing: Bite it -- Bite it (dub version) -- Bite it.
    - Unity (sing it, shout it) Performed by: Tony Aiken, vocals; & the Future 2000, ca.1975; SR-549 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Kimsha Records
      Track listing: Unity (sing it, shout it) -- Good things -- Better days -- She loves me -- Time tunnel.
    - What I like / Two Live Crew Performed by: 2 Live Crew, 1985; SR-550 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Fresh Beat Records
      Track listing: What I like (vocal) -- What I like (instrumental) -- What I like (scratch version).
    - Fresh / Tyrone Brunson Performed by: Tyrone Brunson, guitar, 1984; SR-551 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Believe in a Dream
      Track listing: Fresh -- Fresh (scratch mix).
    - Super-Wolf can do it / Super-Wolf Performed by: Super-Wolf, vocals; with instrumental acc, 1980; SR-552 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Super-Wolf can do it -- Anybody can do it -- Super-Wolf can do it (long version).
    - Rock on / Sugar Kay and the Mighty Three Performed by: Sugar Kay, 1984; SR-553 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Rock on -- Rock on (mix).
    - Wikka wrap: All wrapped up / the Evasions Performed by: Evasions, 1981; SR-554 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Groove Production
      Track listing: Wikka wrap -- All wrapped up.
    - Beatlesongs!: a collection of Beatles novelty records, volume 1 Performed by: Bill Buchanan and Howard Greenfield; Peter Cook and Dudley Moore; the Four Preps; Casey Kasem; Donna Lynn; Jack Nitzsche; the Rutles; Allan Sherman; Gary Usher; Wild Man Fischer; Carefrees; and the Qworymen, 1982; SR-555 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Buchanan and Greenfield / The invasion (2:53) -- The Rutles / Hold my hand (2:31) -- The Carefrees / We love you Beatles (2:18) -- Donna Lynn / My boyfriend got a Beatle haircut (2:12) -- Casey Kasem / Letter from Elaina (3:16) -- Jack Nitzsche / Beatlemania (2:10) -- The Qworymen / Beatle rap (3:55) -- Peter Cook & Dudley Moore / L.S. Bumble Bee (2:42) -- Wild Man Fischer / I'm the meany (1:20) -- Allan Sherman / Pop hates the Beatles (3:04) -- The Four Preps / Letter to the Beatles (2:48) -- Gary Usher / The Beetle (1:54).
    - Monster rap / Bobby (Boris) Pickett; featuring Bobby Paine Performed by: Bobby (Boris) Pickett, featuring Bobby Paine, 1984; SR-556 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Monster rap (club mix) -- Monster rap (dub instrumental).
    - White boy rapp Performed by: Rick Johnston, 1984; SR-557 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Laff
      Track listing: White boy rapp -- Wet dream -- Chantilly lace -- Live stand-up.
    - President's rap / Rich Little Performed by: Rich Little, 1982; SR-558 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Boardwalk
    - To be or not to be (the Hitler rap) / Mel Brooks Performed by: Mel Brooks, 1983; SR-559 (Box 11)
      Track listing: To be or not to be (the Hitler rap) part I -- To be or not to be (instrumental mix) part II.
    - Jocks rap (the passage): Let's dance (the passage) / the Evasions Performed by: Evasions, 1982; SR-560 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Jocks rap (the passage) -- Let's dance (the passage)
    - Roxanne's doctor: the real man / Dr. Freshh Performed by: Dr. Freshh, 1985; SR-561 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Roxanne's doctor: the real man -- Roxanne's doctor: the real man.
    - Roxanne's revenge / Roxanne Shanté Performed by: Roxanne Shanté, 1984; SR-562 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Roxanne's revenge (street version) -- Roxanne's revenge (inst. street version) -- Roxanne's revenge (vocal) -- Roxanne's revenge (instrumental).
    - Party scene / the Russell Brothers Performed by: Russell Brothers, 1983; SR-563 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Portrait
      Track listing: The party scene (SV) -- The party scene (single edit) -- The party scene (instrumental) -- The party scene (LV).
    - Smurf for what it's worth / the Smurfs Performed by: Smurfs, 1983; SR-564 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Smurf for what it's worth -- Smurf for what it's worth.
    - Sparky's turn / Sparky "D" Performed by: Sparky Dee, 1985; SR-565 (Box 11)
      Publisher: NIA Records
      Track listing: Sparky's turn (vocal) -- Sparky's turn (dub) --Sparky's turn (instrumental).
    - Roxanne's a man / Ralph Rolle Performed by: Ralph Rolle, 1985; SR-566 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Roxanne's a man (the untold story -- final chapter) -- Roxanne's a man (dub version).
    - Big fat bottom / Redd Hott Performed by: Redd Hott, 1981; SR-567 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Venture
      Track listing: Big fat bottom -- Big fat bottom (instrumental).
    - Romeo: Roxanne's groove / the Real Roxanne with Howie Tee Performed by: Real Roxanne, 1985; SR-568 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Romeo (part I) -- Romeo (part II) -- Roxanne's groove.
    - Battle / Sparky Dee vs the Playgirls Performed by: Sparky Dee, 1985; SR-569 (Box 11)
      Track listing: The battle -- The battle (dub).
    - New rap language: Love rap / Spoonie Gee and the Treacherous Three Performed by: Spoonie Gee and the Treacherous Three; with instrumental acc, 1980; SR-570 (Box 11)
      Track listing: The new rap language -- Love rap.
    - Placin' the beat / Spyder-D; featuring D.J. Divine Performed by: Spyder-D, 1984; SR-571 (Box 11)
      Publisher: ZYX Records
      Track listing: Placin' the beat -- Placin' the beat (instrumental).
    - Smerphies dance / Spyder-D Performed by: Spyder-D, 1984; SR-572 (Box 11)
      Track listing: Smerphies dance -- Smerphies dance (make your own rap).
    - Smerphies dance / Spyder-D Performed by: Spyder-D, ca. 1985; SR-573 (Box 11)
      Publisher: Telestar Cassettes
  - LPs - SR 574-623 (Box 12)
    - Unity (in the place to be): Hollis rock / Spyder C Performed by: Spyder C, 1983; SR-574 (Box 12)
      Publisher: West End
      Track listing: Unity (in the place to be) (vocal) -- Hollis rock (vocal) -- Unity (in the place to be) (instrumental) -- Hollis rock (instrumental).
    - Take your radio / Steady "B" Performed by: Steady B, ca. 1985; SR-575 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Take your radio (vocal) -- Take your radio (instrumental).
    - Station brake: Intermission / Captain Sky Performed by: Captain Sky, 1981; SR-576 (Box 12)
      Publisher: WMOT Records
      Track listing: Station brake -- Intermission.
    - Talkin' out the side of your neck: She's strange (rap version) / Cameo Performed by: Cameo, 1984; SR-577 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Atlanta Artists
      Track listing: Talkin' out the side of your neck -- She's strange (rap version).
    - Dazzle your mind: New York fresh beats / the Bug Out Boys with Nick Eastside Performed by: Bug Out Boys, 1985; SR-578 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Col' Rock Stuf Records
      Track listing: Dazzle your mind -- New York fresh beats.
    - Matt's mood: Matt's cool; Everybody break; Break, break / the Breekout Krew Performed by: Breekout Krew, 1984; SR-579 (Box 12)
      Publisher: London; Next Plateau Records
      Track listing: Matt's mood (street mix) -- Matt's cool (rock beats) -- Everybody break (fresh beats) -- Break, break (up-rock free style).
    - Clubin tonight / Boyz Club Performed by: Boyz Club, ca. 1980; SR-580 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Klubb House
      Track listing: Club mix -- Booby mix -- Friday mix -- Vocal jam mix.
    - Monster rap / Bobby (Boris) Pickett; featuring Bobby Paine Performed by: Pickett, Bobby (Boris), 1985; SR-581 (Box 12)
    - Taste of chocolate / Big Daddy Kane Performed by: Big Daddy Kane, with accompaniment, 1990; SR-582 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Cold Chillin' Records: Manufactured and distributed by Reprise Records
      Track listing: Taste of chocolate: intro (2:05) -- Cause I can do it right (4:09) -- It's hard being the Kane (4:58) -- Who am I (featuring Gamilah Shabazz) (4:00) -- Dance with the devil (4:06) -- No damn good (3:52) -- All of me (featuring Barry White) (5:45) -- Keep 'em on the floor (featuring Barbara Weathers) (4:32) -- Mr. Pitiful (3:26) -- Put your weight on it (2:46) -- Big Daddy vs. Dolemite (featuring Rudy Ray Moore) (4:49) -- Down the line (5:11) -- Taste of chocolate: exit (3:20).
    - It's hard being the Kane / Big Daddy Kane Performed by: Big Daddy Kane, 1990; SR-583 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Cold Chillin'
      Track listing: It's hard being the Kane (remix radio version) -- It's hard being the Kane (remix radio version w/ fade).
    - Ooh, aah, nah-nah-nah / Big Daddy Kane Performed by: Big Daddy Kane, 1991; SR-584 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Ooh, aah, nah-nah-nah (master mix) -- Ooh, aah, nah-nah-nah (master mix).
    - Get into it: Somethin' funky; Just rhymin' with biz / Big Daddy Kane Performed by: Big Daddy Kane, 1987; SR-585 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Get into it (vocal) -- Get into it (instrumental) -- Somethin' funky -- Just rhymin' with biz.
    - Raw; Word to the mother (land) / Big Daddy Kane Performed by: Big Daddy Kane, vocals; with instrumental acc, 1987; SR-586 (Box 12)
      Track listing: Raw -- Word to the mother (land) -- Raw (dubapella).
    - Be bop rock / the Beat Boys Performed by: Beat Boys, 1983; SR-587 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Sugarscoop
      Track listing: Be bop rock -- Be bop rock (part 2).
    - Shake it up ('til ya drop) / Barone Performed by: Barone, 1984; SR-588 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Silver Blue Records
      Track listing: Shake it up ('til ya drop) -- Shake it up ('til ya drop) (dub mix).
    - Spooks in space / Aural Exciters Performed by: Aural Exciters, 1979; SR-589 (Box 12)
      Publisher: ZE Records
      Track listing: Spooks in space -- (He's a) marathon runner -- Goin' to a showdown -- Maladie d'amour -- Emil (night rate) -- Spooks in space (discomix).
    - Everyday people: the breakbeat party album / Afrika Bambaataa & Timezone Performed by: Afrika Bambaataa, 2004; SR-590 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Planet Rock Music
      Track listing: The alien -- Spank it -- Well -- Alright -- Push pt. 2 -- Bambaataa's theme part 2 -- No nonsense song (instrumental) -- Zulu Bronx River -- The jam -- Say ho -- Bongo rock millenium -- Stranga (vocal) -- Stranga (funk rap) -- Everybody -- Walk on by (live in Texas) -- Everyday people.
    - Original style Performed by: Various performers, ca. 2000; SR-591 (Box 12)
      Publisher: New Star
      Track listing: Do it anyway (Mike T) -- Get up (Pookey Blow) -- Super rock body shock (Eye Beta Rock) -- The ultimate rap (Nice & Nasty 3) -- One time two time blow my mind (MC Rock Lovely) -- Be for real (Denyce Flip Isaac) -- You've got the power (South Bronx Movement) -- Oh yeah (The Jackson Two) -- M (Missy Dee & the Melody Crew) -- Rock the message rap (Keeling Bedford Connection) -- One million dollar legs (Outlaw Four) -- At the place to be (Mr. Sweety).
    - Rap tracks Performed by: Various performers, 1982; SR-592 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Virgin
      Track listing: Station brake (Captain Sky) -- Here to stay (me and my double R.R.) (Count Coolout) -- Double Dutch bus (Frankie Smith) -- Can you feel it (Funk Fusion Band) -- Calling doctor ice (Doctor Ice) -- Enjoy with me (Midnight Blue) -- Put the boogie in your body (Treacherous Three) -- Do it, do it (Disco Four).
    - Rap archives legends, volume 1 Performed by: Various performers, 1996; SR-593 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Sounds of Urban London Records
      Track listing: Intro -- Slick Rick and Doug E. Fresh at the Lincoln Project, NY 1984 -- Zulu Nation Anniversary at the Roxy, Bronx, NY 1984 -- Force MC's at the Harlem World, Manhattan, NY 1981 -- Kool Moe Dee vs. Busy Bee at the Harlem World, Manhattan, NY 1981 -- Fruitkwan vs. Roxanne, New Music Seminar 1986 -- Biz Markie & Big Daddy Kane at the Masonic Temple, NY 1986 -- Kool Moe Dee & TLS Rock at LL Cool J's B'day lan, Philly 1987 -- LL Cool J at LL Cool J's B'day lan, Philly 1987 -- Master Don at the YMCA, Manhattan, NY 1983 -- Run-DMC at Madison Square Gardens, NY 1986 -- DJ Cheese live at UK Fresh, Wembley, London, England 1986 -- Boogie Down Productions at the Masonic Temple, NY 1986 -- The message, the word!!
    - Gonh be funky / Lee Dorsey Performed by: Lee Dorsey, 1980; SR-594 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Charly
      Track listing: Working in the coal mine -- Holy cow -- Do-re-mi -- A lover was born -- Give it up -- Can you hear me -- Freedom for the stallion -- Ride your pony -- Get out of my life woman -- Ya ya -- Love lots of lovin' -- Candy yam -- Go-go girl -- You're breaking me up -- On your way down -- Everything I do gonh be funky.
    - Prep rap / Russ Mason Performed by: Russ Mason, 1981; SR-595 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Nemperor Records
      Track listing: Prep rap (instrumental) -- Prep rap.
    - Let's rock / Harlem World Crew Performed by: Harlem World, ca. 1985; SR-596 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Tay-Ster
      Track listing: Let's rock (5:56) -- Let's rock (3:30).
    - Rock the message rap / Grand Master Chilly T & Stevie G Back to back / Keeling Beckford Connection Performed by: Grand Master Chilly T, 1981; SR-597 (Box 12)
      Publisher: 12 Star Records; Distributed by Arawak Record
    - Play that beat, Mr. D.J. / GLOBE & Whiz Kid Performed by: GLOBE and Whiz Kid, 1983; SR-598 (Box 12)
    - Baya Latinos / PJ LaBoy Performed by: PJ LaBoy, ca. 1975; SR-599 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Etc. Records
      Track listing: Baya Latinos -- Baya Latinos (instrumental) (do your own rap)
    - More ounce rap Performed by: Various performers, 1980; SR-600 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Scorpio; Distributed by D and K Productions
      Track listing: More ounce -- Magic rap -- Do it rap -- Another rap -- Party rap -- Bugs-B-Skate -- Time rap -- Down rap.
    - Million dollar legs (rap) / Outlaw Four Performed by: Outlaw Four, ca. 1985; SR-601 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Dynamite PEP Records
    - Rappin it up / by First Class Performed by: First Class; Dancin' Willie, Moe Meek, 1979; SR-602 (Box 12)
      Publisher: First Class
    - Rules of the game / Juny Boom Performed by: Juny Boom, 1981; SR-603 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Snowflake Records
      Track listing: Rules of the game -- Rules of the game (Instrumental)
    - Techno-freqs; T-Freqan / Junie Morrison Performed by: Junie, 1984; SR-604 (Box 12)
      Publisher: BWay
      Track listing: Techno-freqs -- Techno-freqs (short version) -- T-freqan (dub)
    - Ain't no thing / Steinski Say Ho! / J Rocc Performed by: J Rocc, 2004; SR-605 (Box 12)
      Publisher: Stones Throw Records